EREN DORU

FRONTEND DEV.



+90 553 831 4101



erendoru@hotmail.com



Kocaeli / Körfez Esentepe Mah. Hamit Kaplan cad. No:160 Daire:1



www.github.com/erendoru



https://www.linkedin.com/in/eren-doru-196535116/



www.dribbble.com/d0ru

SUMMARY

I focus on Frontend Development. I love the design and making a product better. REACTJS has been a quick gamechanger for me. My approach is plain/simple: I don't plan to reinvent the wheel or impress you with overengineering. I am a quick learner and I love navigating new frameworks & libraries.

SKILLS

Languages

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS

Tools

- ReactJS, NextJS
- Context, Redux
- Webpack
- SASS, SCSS

Performance & Testing Frameworks

- Jest
- ReactTesting Library

Backend

- Learning google cloud techs.
- Fiebase (Cloud API, Firestore)

Design

• Figma

Version Control Systems

• Git & Github

PROJECTS

WEATHER APP

I built a functional weather app that not only do basic weather info. You can change location, fahrenheit to celcius, 5 days forecast wether, humidity by percentage. Fully responsive and functional.

Skills: ReactJS, HTML, SASS, Axios, Iconify, Git, Github

Github: www.github.com/erendoru/Weather-App

Demo: https://weather-app-eight-chi.vercel.app/ -- WeatherAPI ended due to this problem it does not load data properly

TWITTER CLONE

With new technologies on ReactJS I made a fully responsive and functional twitter clone.

Skills: NextJS, Storybook, PostCSS, Style Loader

Github: www.github.com/erendoru/twitter-web-

Demo: https://twitter-clone-silk-eta.vercel.app/

CORONA TRACKER APP

Using covid19 api and ReactJS I made a covid19 data tracker app.

Skills: ReactJS, Axios, ChartJS, Html, Css

Github: www.github.com/erendoru/corona-

tracker

Demo: https://corona-tracker-

example.vercel.app/

AREAS OF EXPERTISE INCLUDE:

- UI Designing
- Coding
- Application Designing
- Debugging
- Performance improvement
- Feature Designing
- Webpage Optimization
- Webpage Designing

• TRAVEL WEBSITE EXAMPLE

Using ReactJS I made fully responsive travel agent website.

Skills: ReactJS, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Github: www.github.com/erendoru/React-

website-example

Demo: https://react-website-eta-

orcin.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

KOCAELI UNIVERSITY

Beden Eğitimi Öğretmenliği 2015 - 2019 Abondoned

KOCAELI UNIVERSITY

Computer Programming 2017 - 2019

DOGUS UNIVERSITY

Computer Engineering - English 2020 - Continues DoüStartup

LANGUAGES

Turkish: NativeEnglish: Fluent

PTE Academic Score: 68

IELTS: 7.2

CERTIFICATES

\$50's Introduction to Computer Science

EDx October 2020

Responsive Web Design

FreeCodecamp November 2019 www.freecodecamp.org/certification/d0ru/responsive-web-design

Javascript

Sololearn April 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Akinon

Frontend Developer - Full Time Remote

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

I work for the service team at Akinon, where we service for a variety of brands, including Penti, A101, Panço, and Vilebrequin. Tech:Javascript, Html, Css, Jinja

Pufero - Founder

March 2021 - Sep 2022

E-Commerce business
A new brand and product for the market.
We sell in the biggest e-commerce websites in Turkey.
Trendyol.com - Pufero
Hepsiburada.com - Pufero
www.pufero.com

Bizim Internet

Frontend Developer - Intern

July 2019 - Sep 2019

It was my first time learning ReactJS, we remake the customer app with ReactJS Tech: HTML, CSS, JS, REACTJS